<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="93">
  <author>FearlessStudios</author>
  <version>1.1.0.0</version>
  <title>
    <en>Liquid Lime</en>
    <de>Flüssigkalk</de>
    <fr>Chaux Liquide</fr>
    <cz>Tekuté Vápno</cz>
  </title>
  
  <description>
    <en><![CDATA[Liquid Lime

Revolutionize your farming experience with Liquid Lime, specially formulated for use with sprayers.

NOTE: This is not working correctly with helpers so please do not use them with Liquid Lime. (Looking into a way to make them work correctly if it is possible)

Key Features:
- Liquid Lime Fill Type:
  - Adds Liquid Lime to the game as a new material compatible with sprayers.

Items:
- TrueEdge Liquid Lime Tank:
  - Capacity: 2000 liters
  - Price: $900
- Meridian Liquid Lime Silo:
  - Capacity: 155,000 liters
  - Price: $46,500
  - Daily upkeep: $100
- TrueEdge Liquid Lime Production:
  - Price: $42,500
  - Daily upkeep: $100
  - Liquid Lime recipe: LIME and WATER

Liquid Lime provides a practical and efficient solution for soil treatment, aiming to replicate the characteristics of real liquid lime as closely as possible.

Please report any issues you may have here: https://github.com/FearlessNite345/FS25_Liquid_Lime/issues

Changelog v1.1.0.0:
- Added a new production to produce Liquid Lime with Lime and Water. (This can bring cost savings)
- Increased the Liquid Lime Silo storage capacity from 140,000 liters to 155,000 liters.
- Added Liquid Lime to mks8 & mks32. (these are under my custom brand TrueEdge.)]]>
    </en>
    <de><![CDATA[Flüssigkalk

Revolutionieren Sie Ihr Farming-Erlebnis mit Flüssigkalk, speziell entwickelt für den Einsatz mit Sprühgeräten.

HINWEIS: Dies funktioniert nicht korrekt mit Helfern, daher verwenden Sie diese bitte nicht mit Liquid Lime.

Hauptmerkmale:
- Flüssigkalk-Fülltyp:
  - Fügt Flüssigkalk als neues Material hinzu, das mit Sprühgeräten kompatibel ist.

Objekte:
- TrueEdge Flüssigkalk-Tank:
  - Kapazität: 2000 Liter
  - Preis: 900 €
- Meridian Flüssigkalk-Silo:
  - Kapazität: 155.000 Liter
  - Preis: 46.500 €
  - Täglicher Unterhalt: 100 €
-TrueEdge Flüssigkalkproduktion:
  - Preis: 42.500 $
  - Täglicher Unterhalt: 100 €
  - Rezept für Flüssigkalk: KALK und WASSER

Flüssigkalk bietet eine praktische und effiziente Lösung zur Bodenbehandlung und wurde entwickelt, um die Eigenschaften von echtem Flüssigkalk so genau wie möglich nachzubilden.

Bitte melden Sie alle Probleme hier: https://github.com/FearlessNite345/FS25_Liquid_Lime/issues

Änderungsprotokoll v1.1.0.0:
- Neue Produktion hinzugefügt, um Liquid Lime mit Kalk und Wasser herzustellen. (Dies kann Kosteneinsparungen bringen)
- Erhöhung der Lagerkapazität des Liquid Lime Silos von 140.000 Litern auf 155.000 Liter.
- Liquid Lime zu mks8 und mks32 hinzugefügt. (Diese gehören zu meiner benutzerdefinierten Marke TrueEdge.)]]>
    </de>
    <fr><![CDATA[Chaux liquide

Révolutionnez votre expérience agricole avec de la chaux liquide, spécialement conçue pour les pulvérisateurs.

REMARQUE: Cela ne fonctionne pas correctement avec les assistants, veuillez donc ne pas les utiliser avec le Liquid Lime.

Caractéristiques clés :
- Type de remplissage de chaux liquide :
  - Ajoute de la chaux liquide au jeu en tant que nouveau matériau compatible avec les pulvérisateurs.

Objets :
- TrueEdge Réservoir de chaux liquide :
  - Capacité : 2000 litres
  - Prix : 900 €
- Meridian Silo à chaux liquide :
  - Capacité : 155 000 litres
  - Prix : 46 500 €
  - Entretien quotidien : 100 €
- Production de chaux liquide TrueEdge :
  - Prix : 42 500 $
  - Entretien quotidien : 100 €
  - Recette de chaux liquide : CHAUX et EAU

La chaux liquide offre une solution pratique et efficace pour le traitement des sols, reproduisant les caractéristiques de la véritable chaux liquide avec précision.

Veuillez signaler tout problème ici : https://github.com/FearlessNite345/FS25_Liquid_Lime/issues

Journal des modifications v1.1.0.0 :
- Ajout d'une nouvelle production pour produire du Liquid Lime avec de la chaux et de l'eau. (Cela peut générer des économies de coûts)
- Augmentation de la capacité de stockage du silo Liquid Lime de 140 000 litres à 155 000 litres.
- Ajout du Liquid Lime aux mks8 et mks32. (Ces derniers font partie de ma marque personnalisée TrueEdge.)]]>
    </fr>
  </description>
  
  <iconFilename>icon_liquidLime.dds</iconFilename>
  
  <multiplayer supported="true" />

  <l10n>
    <text name="filltype_liquidlime">
      <en>Liquid Lime</en>
      <de>Flüssigkalk</de>
      <fr>Chaux Liquide</fr>
      <cz>Tekuté Vápno</cz>
    </text>
    <text name="function_liquidlimepallet">
      <en>Liquid Lime Tank allows you to fill sprayers with Liquid Lime.</en>
      <de>Flüssigkalk-Tank ermöglicht das Befüllen von Sprühgeräten mit Flüssigkalk.</de>
      <fr>Le réservoir de chaux liquide permet de remplir les pulvérisateurs avec de la chaux liquide.</fr>
      <cz>Nádrž na tekuté vápno umožňuje plnit postřikovače tekutým vápnem.</cz>
    </text>
    <text name="function_liquidlimesilo">
      <en>Liquid Lime Silo provides storage and refill capabilities for Liquid Lime.</en>
      <de>Flüssigkalk-Silo bietet Lagerung und Nachfüllmöglichkeiten für Flüssigkalk.</de>
      <fr>Le silo à chaux liquide offre des capacités de stockage et de remplissage pour la chaux liquide.</fr>
      <cz>Silo na tekuté vápno poskytuje možnosti skladování a doplňování tekutého vápna.</cz>
    </text>
    <text name="function_liquidlimeproduction">
      <en>You can make Liquid Lime or Lime using water and stones.</en>
      <de>Sie können Flüssigkalk oder Kalk mit Wasser und Steinen herstellen.</de>
      <fr>Vous pouvez fabriquer de la chaux liquide ou de la chaux avec de l'eau et des pierres.</fr>
      <cz>Pomocí vody a kamenů můžete vyrobit tekuté vápno nebo vápno.</cz>
    </text>
    <text name="name_liquidlimeproduction">
      <en>Liquid Lime Production</en>
      <de>Flüssigkalkproduktion</de>
      <fr>Production de Chaux Liquide</fr>
      <cz>Výroba tekutého vápna</cz>
    </text>
  </l10n>

  <extraSourceFiles>
    <sourceFile filename="scripts/LiquidLime.lua" />
  </extraSourceFiles>

  <storeItems>
    <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/LiquidLimeTank/multiPurchaseLiquidTank_liquidLimeTank.xml" />
    <storeItem xmlFilename="objects/LiquidLimeTank/liquidLimeTank.xml" />
    <storeItem xmlFilename="placeables/LiquidLimeSilo/liquidLimeSilo.xml" />
    <storeItem xmlFilename="placeables/LiquidLimeProduction/liquidLimeProduction.xml" />
    <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/trueedge_mks8/trueedge_mks8.xml" />
    <storeItem xmlFilename="vehicles/trueedge_mks32/trueedge_mks32.xml" />
  </storeItems>

  <brands>
    <brand name="TRUEEDGE" title="TrueEdge" image="brand/brand_TRUEEDGE.dds" />
  </brands>

  <fillTypes filename="xml/fillTypes.xml" />
</modDesc>
